Hello friends, my name is Anil Rajpurohit
and today I am presenting to you
Tata Life Insurance's
Fortuner Guarantee Plus plan. This is a
guaranteed plan where you
can get long term income for a long time and all the
benefits will be guaranteed in it.
Let us know all the
benefits and features of this plan. If you
like my video, then subscribe to my YouTube channel Anil Rajbhar
Triple FS and like it. The
first beneficial feature of the Lion Plan is
that its income is hundred percent
guaranteed. It will be
written in writing on the policy bond that all your
benefits, which is your annual income, will be
100 percent guaranteed. The
second big benefit of this policy is that it also provides coverage for 40 major
diseases. You
can also purchase a rider separately in this and
two options are given in it. The second option
also provides the benefit of critical illness. If
you pay the premium, then your policy term
i.e. when the period of taking your income is over,
after that whatever premium
payment you have made  The amount invested will be returned to you 100%.
In this policy, you can
also avail tax benefit under section 80C of income tax.
If you fall in the 30% income tax
slab, then a large amount
of your income can also be deducted from income tax and the
income that is returned to you every year will be returned to you under the section of income tax.
You can pay the premium in this policy as per your convenience. You
can now pay the premium annually.
You can take 6-monthly premium payment. You
can pay the premium quarterly for three months and you can
also take the option of monthly premium payment. The
frequency of taking income in the policy can also be decided from the first year
whether you would
like to take the income you get together annually or every
month. You will be
given both the options of taking annual and monthly income. If
you want more benefits in this policy, then you
can get a rider by paying an additional premium. In this, you have a rider for accidental death, a rider for
disabilities and a
rider for speaker, there is a rider for term and terminal, so in
this way,
according to the critical  You can get
your insurance done through the
Hindu option of taking a policy for a
regular income which will give you income every year
and along with a regular income, the
benefit of these serious diseases has also been given in
this, there is coverage of 40 major diseases as well,
if you get any of these diseases
then you are waived from paying the premium
and you start getting income immediately, the
second option is that you can take the plan for
both husband and wife in a single policy, you
can take the benefit, you can
take the feature of joint life, in a single policy the
husband will get the income first, if the husband dies
then the wife will get the income and if she dies then
whatever money is lost will be
returned to the family, this is a very good
feature,
if you want to take the husband wife joint life also because
in this type of benefit you get pension plan,
when there is no 10 times insurance tax in pension plan, that
is, the
pension coming in is taxable, but here you will
get 10 times the insurance company,
insurance tax is also applicable and
tax is also applicable on the coming pension.  Both husband and
wife are getting the benefit of income in this.
You can also select the income term keeping in mind the goals of your life, whether
you want income for
20 years, 25 years, 30 years,
35 years,
40, 45 years. Now first of all you
can select for how many years I will
pay the premium and for how many years I want income. You can decide the
income as per your wish, you
can do it as per your goal.
You will also be
given many different options for premium payment. You will get
an option of limited pay. You will get the option of regular pay. You will
also be given the option of making different premium payments for 5 years, 6 years, 7 years, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12 years in limited pay. You
can pay as many premiums as per your constitution. You can
also leave a will for your family members and loved ones.
What happens in this policy is that as long as
you are alive  You will get income
but if the
life insured in the policy dies, even then the
income that was there will continue to come, the
family will keep getting it and the
money that was to be received at the end will also be received by the family.
What are the other features in both the options in the policy, the first option is
regular income, the second is the option with inbuilt critical
illness benefit,
what will be the entry in both, a person of one year can
purchase it in regular income and if he
wants to take the inbuilt critical illness policy option, then the
minimum age should be 18 years,
maximum a person of 60 years can purchase this policy,
if we talk about
income of you, then in the first option
we can take income of 20, 25, 30, 35, 40, 45 years
and if we look at the option of inbuilt critical illness
benefit, then if you have to
pay for 5 years, then you
can take income for up to 30 years, if you pay for 10 years, pay the
premium, then you
can take income for 25 years,
now let's see you
Why should one take Tata Insurance policy? It is a
very big brand.
Its asset management is also 62000 crores. It has an asset
management of 62000 crores. They are
managing such a huge amount of money that people have paid as premium.
Till now, they have protected 68 lakh families by
giving them policies. It has
more than 400 branches across India.
Its claim settlement ratio is 98.53%.
They guarantee to clear the claim within 4 hours.
If you have submitted the correct documents on
time, then you
can get the claim settled within 4 hours. It is the
fastest in the industry. It settles the claim accordingly.
Tata will do it
if you have submitted all the documents on time
and you can select the payment method as per your convenience.
Now let us understand the illustrations of our product. The
first option is Regular Income
Option and the second option is Regular Income with
Critical Investment. How do these two options work? Let us
understand both of them.
First of all, here you will see the problem of a
customer.  Whose age is 35 and here he is
selecting the regular option,
what are the benefits of the regular option, he is paying the premium for 12 years, the
policy term is 13 years, which means he is taking a development plan of one year
and he is selecting the product Guarantee
Plus Tata,
here you will see that
income will come and here he also takes different riders,
in this there is a rider for accidental death, right hand
permanent disabilities,
that rider is also critical, if you want to add it then
you can also add riders as per your
need, if you do not want to add it then it will be fine,
he will pay a premium of Rs 1 lakh each for 12 years,
from the first year he will get an
insurance tax of Rs 12 lakh,
after paying the premium for 12 years, one has to wait for one year
and from the 14th year,
income of Rs 1 lakh 32330 will keep coming every year for 30 years
and on maturity
you will get back the Rs 12 lakh paid, so 1323
will add Rs 132000  1332
is finally returned to you and these will be the full
benefits, they will be 100% guaranteed, there will be no
bonus, there will be no
relation with the stock market, here you
can also see the Surendra value, now suppose if the
customer dies in his sleep year then what will happen is that he will
get Rs 12 lakhs, the policy will be cancelled
but suppose if it happens after 15 years then the
remaining income that was to come will keep coming to the nominee, the family members
and the
maturity amount will also be given to the family members, so there is an
insurance tax of 12 lakhs,
but now here instead of ₹132000, the
income is coming of 92140 because your rider
is also inbuilt, that critical insurance is given in it
and the money lost on maturity is
returned, so now here let us assume
that the customer paid three premiums and the
customer died, okay on this date
all the remaining premiums will be waived
and the income that you were going to get is 92000, right?
From this year, income of Rs 92,000 will start coming from the
third year onwards. Because if you
die shortly after the premium is paid in the third year, then
you will
start getting an income of Rs 92,140 from the third year onwards and
it will continue for the entire 25 years. And
on maturity, because if you die after paying three premiums, then you will
also get Rs 3 lakh on maturity. In
this way, you can select
any of the two options as per your need.
If I summarize it, then this
is a good plan where you can
pay the premium as per your convenience and can get the income. The income will be
guaranteed. Saving rates are
decreasing with time. In 2000, the rates of HD were
around 10-30 percent. Now, if you
look at the average rates for different periods of time, less than 5 years, then the
rates are quite low. In the future, it may decrease further,
but the income you get from this policy will remain the
same forever.
If you have purchased the policy at this time, the
income you are getting at this time is the
income for that period.  It will be fixed for that many years, the
rate will never decrease, after taking the policy
you will also get income tax benefits
and you will
also get benefits from many additional riders,
so if you want to purchase this policy,
I am Anil Rajput, then you
can complete the policy by contacting me on mobile number 9909403412 and if you
want to get more information about the plan, then you
can also get information about the plan on your mobile phone by paying me a little consultancy fee, if you
liked my video then do subscribe to my YouTube channel